<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on Eralp Sahin</title><link>https://eralpsahin.com/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on Eralp Sahin</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://eralpsahin.com/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deanonymizing Anonymous Users on Piazza Q&amp;A</title><link>https://eralpsahin.com/blog/deanonymizing-anonymous-users-on-piazza-qa/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eralpsahin.com/blog/deanonymizing-anonymous-users-on-piazza-qa/</guid><description>Home Blog Projects Deanonymizing Anonymous Users on Piazza Q&amp;A My TAship Experience Piazza Anonymity on Piazza User Statistics on Piazza Piazza API Unravel How does it work? Demo Video Limitations Footnotes Deanonymizing Anonymous Users on Piazza Q&amp;amp;A Unravel - Deanonymize anonymous Users on Piazza Q&amp;amp;A.</description></item><item><title>XCode 11</title><link>https://eralpsahin.com/blog/xcode-11/</link><pubDate>Tue, 18 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eralpsahin.com/blog/xcode-11/</guid><description>Home Blog Projects XCode 11 Wiki New Features Minimap Editor Focus Documentation Swift Package Manager Recall WWDC 2018 Commands Demo SwiftPM Integration References XCode 11 Wiki My personal notes on
Getting Started with XCode What’s new in XCode 11 Debugging in Xcode 11 sessions from WWDC 2019.</description></item><item><title>GNU Make Wiki</title><link>https://eralpsahin.com/blog/gnu-make-wiki/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eralpsahin.com/blog/gnu-make-wiki/</guid><description>Home Blog Projects GNU Make Wiki Glossary Makefile Rule Syntax Simple Rule Prerequisites Useful command-line options References GNU Make Wiki This markdown is a sketched summary of the Managing Projects with GNU Make.1
Glossary Target: Usually the name of the file generated by the command, sometimes the name of the action such as clean.</description></item><item><title>Coding Interview University</title><link>https://eralpsahin.com/blog/coding-interview-university/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://eralpsahin.com/blog/coding-interview-university/</guid><description>Home Blog Projects Coding Interview University Progress Tracking Don’t feel you aren’t smart enough Interview Process Languages I will study Readings related to this Topic Before you Get Started You Won’t Remember it All Use Flashcards Cheatsheets and review, review, review Prerequisite Knowledge The Daily Plan Algorithmic Complexity Book List Interview Prep Language Specific Tool Specific Software Engineering Data Structures More Knowledge Sorting Graphs Even More Knowledge Final Review Coding Challenges System Design Main resources Scalability Your Resume Networking and Job Applications Close to Interview Be thinking of for when the interview comes Have questions for the interviewer Additional Learning Additional Detail on Some Subjects Video Series Papers References Coding Interview University Forked from John Washam.</description></item></channel></rss>